A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1990
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals, 1990
Library of Virginia
34147
5 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restorations of rights, pardons granted, extradition renditions and requisitions are restricted (public access and photoduplication) to those with written authorization from the Secretary of the Commonwealth. Guide to the collection available in Archives Manuscript Room.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth on April 17, 1992.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth has evolved from early colonial times when there existed a Secretary of the Colony. Thomas Nelson held the position of the first Secretary of Virginia in 1776. Early Secretaries were elected by the public. An Act of the General Assembly in 1920 changed the election to a joint vote of the General Assembly. In a 1930 Act the duties of the Secretary were redefined with the Secretary of the Commonwealth serving as the ex officio secretary of the Governor, as custodian of many official State records, and as keeper of the Greater and Lesser Seals of the Commonwealth. The office of the Secretary has gradually acquired other functions, such as: service of out-of-state civil process; appointment and regulation of notaries public; and registration and oversight of lobbyists. The Office became a gubernational appointment subsequent to a 1958 Act of the Assembly. The Secretary of the Commonwealth is under the jurisdiction of the Governor's Office.
The Secretary is appointed by the Governor for a term of four years. The Secretary has an Executive assistant and an Assistant who is in charge of prison mail and research duties. The Chief Clerk is responsible for the Governor's Journal and extraditions and acts as general office manager. Major activities are: serving as ex officio Secretary to the Governor; serving as the keeper of the seals of the Commonwealth; compiling and publishing the annual Blue Book; commissioning and regulating notary publics, including the publication of a Notary Handbook and conduct of disciplinary hearings; promulgating the lobbying disclosure requirements, registration of lobbyst, and recording of lobbying reports; servicing the civil process of out-of-state defendants and other parties; and authenticating and certifying the records of the courts and of any state agency.
Scope and Content
These records are the permanent record of the Governor's appointments, executive orders and memorandums, commissions, notaries, pardons, proclamations, writs of election, restoration of rights, renditions and requisitions as recorded by the Secretary of the Commonwealth. This accession consists of the records of the first year of Governor Lawrence D. Wilder's administration (January-December, 1990).
Arrangement
The records for Governor Wilder are arranged by date then type of record, alphabetically. Boxes 1-2 are available to researchers. Boxes 3-5, containing restoration of rights, pardons granted, extradition renditions and requisitions, are restricted (public access and photo duplication) to those with written authorization from the Secretary of the Commonwealth.
Contents List
- List of Contents, 1990 January-July (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Notaries, 1990 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Notaries, 1990 January 5 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Notaries, 1990 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Notaries, 1990 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Notaries, 1990 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Notaries, 1990 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Notaries, 1990 January 19 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Notaries, 1990 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Executive order, 1990 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Executive order, 1990 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Executive order, 1990 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Appointment, 1990 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 19 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Notaries, 1990 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Notaries, 1990 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Notaries, 1990 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Executive order, 1990 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Proclamation, 1990 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Appointment, 1990 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Appointment, 1990 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Appointment, 1990 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Appointment, 1990 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 3 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 27 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Notaries, 1990 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Notaries, 1990 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Notaries, 1990 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Notaries, 1990 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Notaries, 1990 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Notaries, 1990 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Notaries, 1990 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Notaries, 1990 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Appointments, 1990 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Appointments, 1990 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Appointments, 1990 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Appointments, 1990 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Appointments, 1990 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Appointments, 1990 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Appointments, 1990 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Notaries, 1990 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Notaries, 1990 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Notaries, 1990 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Notaries, 1990 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Notaries, 1990 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Executive order, 1990 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Executive order, 1990 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Proclamation, 1990 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Appointments, 1990 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Appointments, 1990 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Appointments, 1990 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Appointments, 1990 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Appointments, 1990 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Executive Memo, 1990 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Notaries, 1990 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 163)
- Notaries, 1990 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Notaries, 1990 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Executive Order, 1990 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 166)
- Appointments, 1990 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Appointments, 1990 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Appointments, 1990 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Appointments, 1990 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Appointments, 1990 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Appointments, 1990 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Appointments, 1990 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Appointments, 1990 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Appointments, 1990 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 175)
- Appointments, 1990 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 176)
- Appointments, 1990 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Appointments, 1990 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Appointments, 1990 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 179)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 June 13 (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 181)
- Appointments, Agency heads, 1990 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 182)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 1 (Box 1, Folder 183)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 185)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 188)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 191)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 192)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 193)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 194)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 195)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 196)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 197)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 198)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 200)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 201)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 202)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 203)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 204)
- Notaries, 1990 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 205)
- Notaries, 1990 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Notaries, 1990 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 207)
- Executive Order, 1990 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 208)
- Executive Order, 1990 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 209)
- Executive Order, 1990 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 210)
- Executive Order, 1990 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 211)
- Appointments, 1990 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 212)
- Appointments, 1990 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 213)
- Appointments, 1990 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 214)
- Appointments, 1990 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 215)
- Appointments, 1990 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 216)
- Appointments, 1990 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 217)
- Appointments, 1990 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 218)
- Appointments, 1990 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 219)
- Appointments, 1990 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 220)
- Appointments, 1990 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 221)
- Appointments, 1990 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 222)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 223)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 224)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 225)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 226)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 227)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 228)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 229)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 230)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 231)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 232)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 233)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 234)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 235)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 236)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 237)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 238)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 21 (Box 1, Folder 239)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 240)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 241)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 242)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 243)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 244)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 245)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 246)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 247)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 248)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 249)
- Notaries, 1990 July 13 (Box 1, Folder 250)
- Notaries, 1990 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 251)
- Notaries, 1990 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 252)
- Executive Order, 1990 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 253)
- Executive Order, 1990 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 254)
- Writ of Election, 1990 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 255)
- List of Contents, 1990 August-December (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Appointments, 1990 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Appointments, 1990 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Appointments, 1990 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Appointments, 1990 August 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Appointments, 1990 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Appointments, 1990 August 24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Appointments, 1990 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Appointments, 1990 August 29 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 August 13 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 8 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 13 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 15 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 23 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 24 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 29 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 30 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 August 3 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 August 29 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 August 30 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Notaries, 1990 August 8 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Notaries, 1990 August 14 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Notaries, 1990 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Notaries, 1990 August 24 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Notaries, 1990 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Executive Order, 1990 August 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Executive Order, 1990 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Proclamation, 1990 August 13 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Appointments, 1990 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Appointments, 1990 September 6 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Appointments, 1990 September 14 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Appointments, 1990 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Appointments, 1990 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Appointments, 1990 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Appointments, Agency Heads, 1990 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 5 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 6 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 8 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 14 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 20 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 21 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 25 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 September 6 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 September 26 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Executive Memo, 1990 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Notaries, 1990 September 7 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Notaries, 1990 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Notaries, 1990 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Notaries, 1990 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Appointments, 1990 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Appointments, 1990 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Appointments, 1990 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Appointments, 1990 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Appointments, 1990 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Appointments, 1990 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Appointments, 1990 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 1 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 11 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Appointments, Oaths, 1990 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Appointments, Resignations, 1990 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Notaries, 1990 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 115)